<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LOADays</title><link>https://loadays.org/</link><description>Recent content on LOADays</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://loadays.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Don Bosco Wilrijk</title><link>https://loadays.org/sponsors/donboscowilrijk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/sponsors/donboscowilrijk/</guid><description/></item><item><title>IT Partners</title><link>https://loadays.org/sponsors/itpartners/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/sponsors/itpartners/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Inuits</title><link>https://loadays.org/sponsors/inuits/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/sponsors/inuits/</guid><description/></item><item><title>VanTosh</title><link>https://loadays.org/sponsors/vantosh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/sponsors/vantosh/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Code of Behaviour</title><link>https://loadays.org/codeofbehaviour/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/codeofbehaviour/</guid><description>LOADays is a community conference intended for networking and collaboration in the community of people interested in system engineering and operations.
We value the participation of each member of the community and want all attendees to have an enjoyable and fulfilling experience.
Accordingly, all attendees are expected to show respect and courtesy to other attendees throughout the conference and at all conference events, whether officially sponsored or not.
Exhibitors, speakers, sponsors, staff and all other attendees at LOADays are subject to this Code of Behaviour.</description></item><item><title>Social Event</title><link>https://loadays.org/social/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/social/</guid><description>The social event takes place on Saturday evening after the presentation.
This is also a free event with free food and drinks.
The pizza&amp;rsquo;s are offered by our sponsor IT Partners.</description></item><item><title>Venue</title><link>https://loadays.org/venue/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/venue/</guid><description>Address $ which /location/don_bosco &amp;gt; Don Bosco werken én leren &amp;gt; Valkenveld 70 &amp;gt; 2610 Wilrijk &amp;gt; Belgium By Car Don Bosco Wilrijk is situated next to the A12 Bridge near de Boomsesteenweg (A12) Wilrijk.
Coming from Boom it&amp;rsquo;s on your right, coming from Antwerp it&amp;rsquo;s on your left (straight across Dockx rentals)
Coming from the E19 Take the exit Wilrijk, till you reach Boomse Steenweg (the bridge) then left direction Boom (as above).</description></item><item><title>LOADays CfP 2019 is open.</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_11/</guid><description>The Call-for-Presentation is open for LOADays 2019. The CfP runs till end of March 2019, 31-03-2019. Please take a look on https://cfp.loadays.org/2019/ The event takes place on 4th and 5th of May 2019 in Antwerp, Belgium.</description></item><item><title>Loadays 2019 has new dates!</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_10/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_10/</guid><description>LOADays 2019 is still a GO, however by popular demand we rescheduled LOADays 2019. The new dates are 4th and 5th of May 2019 in Antwerp, Belgium. We&amp;rsquo;ll be opening the CfP shortly.</description></item><item><title>Loadays 2019 is a GO!</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_09/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_09/</guid><description>LOADays 2019 is a GO and will be held on 27th and 28th of April 2018 in Antwerp, Belgium. We&amp;rsquo;ll be opening the CfP shortly.</description></item><item><title>LOADays Schedule 2018 Online</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_08/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_08/</guid><description>The final draft of the LOADays 2018 schedule is online at http://loadays.org/pages/schedule.html</description></item><item><title>Call for Presentations LOADays 2018 Extended!</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_07/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_07/</guid><description>The Call for Presentations, Workshops, Ignites are open for submission. The CfP has been extended and will be open until 8th of April 2018. We decided to run the CfP in git, more specificaly gitlab. Please follow the following process.
Using a Merge Request by following the next steps :
Fork the gitlab project https://git.loadays.eu/2018loadaysbe/cfp Create a new branch Add your proposal to the talk/ or worshop/ or ignite/ dir, a &amp;ldquo;template&amp;rdquo; is available (template.</description></item><item><title>Call for Presentations LOADays 2018!</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_06/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_06/</guid><description>The Call for Presentations, Workshops, Ignites are open for submission. The CfP will be open until 2th of March 2018. We decided to run the CfP in git, more specificaly gitlab. Please follow the following process.
Using a Merge Request by following the next steps :
Fork the gitlab project https://git.loadays.eu/2018loadaysbe/cfp Create a new branch Add your proposal to the talk/ or worshop/ or ignite/ dir, a &amp;ldquo;template&amp;rdquo; is available (template.</description></item><item><title>Loadays 2018 is a GO!</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_05/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_05/</guid><description>LOAD 2018 is a GO and will be held on 21th and 22th of April 2018 in Antwerp, Belgium.</description></item><item><title>LPI @ Loadays</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_04/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_04/</guid><description>As in previous years the Linux Professional Institute (LPI) wants to offer PBT LPI exams at loadays.
LPI Certifications are globally accepted certifications that are:
Designed by a community of Linux professionals, volunteers, vendors and educators. Challenging: if you don&amp;rsquo;t know the subjects you won&amp;rsquo;t pass. Accessible and available at thousands of test centres around the world or at special events. Of high quality: relying on critical input from numerous Linux experts and employing scientific and industry-recognized psychometric processes.</description></item><item><title>Loadays Call for Sponsors</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_03/</guid><description>For the upcoming Loadays we are again looking for sponsors to make this event happen. We rely on sponsoring to help cover costs to accommodate speakers, infrastructure, provide food at affordable prices, etc..
This way we can keep the event free
Levels of sponsorship Bronze (250€) : small logo on the website Silver (500€) : logo on the website and mentioned on mailings to visitors and speakers Gold (750€ +) : Full visibility (logo on website, printed materials) and the ability to speak about your company for 5 minutes at the start of the conference In case you are interested in one of the options above, please drop us an email at info@loadays.</description></item><item><title>Loadays CFP 2015</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_02/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_02/</guid><description>After a successful fifth edition of LOAD, the crew decided to organize a sixth edition.
You are invited to submit a proposal to participate in the 2015 Linux Open Administration Days in Wilrijk, Belgium on April 11 and 12 2015.
More info about how to submit your proposal can be found here
The Linux Open Administration Days is a conference focusing on Linux and Open Administration/engineering. We are trying to fill a gap for System Engineers and Administrators using Open Source technologies.</description></item><item><title>Loadays 2015 is a GO!</title><link>https://loadays.org/posts/post_01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/posts/post_01/</guid><description>LOAD 2015 is a GO and will be held on 11th and 12th of April 2015.</description></item><item><title>About LOADays</title><link>https://loadays.org/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/about/</guid><description>LOADays stands for Linux Open Administration Days and is also referred to as LOAD.
This is an event geared towards Linux and Unix sysadmins and people interested in Free Open Source Linux and Unix system administration, configuration and deployment.
With this event we want to provide a platform for Linux and Unix SysAdmins to get together and share their knowledge and tools.
This is a free event, and therefore there&amp;rsquo;s no entrance fee !</description></item><item><title/><link>https://loadays.org/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://loadays.org/faq/</guid><description>Social Media irc : server freenode channel #loadays twitter : @loadays and during the conference we will use the hashtag #loadays Infrastructure We&amp;rsquo;ll provide internet access for all visitors. SSID : LOAD
Food and Drinks People from the school where the event is taking place will sell drinks, sandwiches and fries at a very reasonable price. There&amp;rsquo;re also some places to eat in the neighborhood.</description></item></channel></rss>